《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on The Flash...
-凯特琳  -爸爸
- Caitlin! - Dad.
我永远爱你
I'll always love you.
你把我们的女儿送回到了未来
You took our daughter back to the future?
我无法相信她
I can't trust her.
斯旺在操纵她
Thawne is manipulating her.
依循我的指示我们就能打败蝉
Follow my instructions and we will defeat Cicada,
摧毁他的匕首
destroy his dagger,
救你的父亲
and save your father.
你创造了自己的神速力
You created your own Speed Force?
是的
Yes, I did.
我可以利用它回到过去
And I can access it to go back in time.
-他怎么能抛下我  -诺拉
- How could he leave me? - Nora--
他怎么可以不再爱我了
How could he stop loving me?
-她消失了  -去了哪里
- She's gone. - Gone where?
我不知道在哪里
I don't know where.
我只知道在什么时候  2019年
I only know when: 2019.
西蒙与伙伴公司
建筑  规划  室内
吉迪恩  扫描服务器已获取
Gideon, scan servers for blueprints
麦克洛奇技术公司的蓝图
from McCulloch Technologies.
找到你了
Gotcha.
吉迪恩  渗透分析
Gideon, infiltration analysis.
是  诺拉·韦斯特·艾伦
Yes, Nora West-Allen.
你独自到达目的地的成功率是
The odds of accessing this location on your own
三百万分之一
are 1 in 3 million.
是否向巴里·艾伦发送请求
Shall I send a request to Barry Allen?
不用  吉迪恩
No, Gideon.
我需要能真正帮到我的人
I need people who can actually help me.
闪 电 侠
第五季
第二十集
超光子扫描仪在城内
Tachyon scanners set up
每隔半英里设置一台
at every half-mile interval across the city.
地震仪正在搜寻
And the seismometer is searching for sonic booms
一百兆赫以内的音爆
in the hundred-megahertz range.
至于卫星  我已经让凯里  夏洛特
As for the satellites, I've got Carrie, Charlotte,
米兰达和萨曼莎持续观测
Miranda, and Samantha scanning
她标志性的黄紫闪电
for her yellow-purple lightning signatures.
我显然是我们小组的萨曼莎  对吧
I am clearly the Samantha of this group, right?
行  可以  米兰达
Yeah, okay, Miranda.
所以技术上来说  如果诺拉使用神速力
So, technically, if Nora uses the Speed Force--
我们就会找到她
We'll find her.
扫描中...
感觉她要突然出现似的
Kinda thought she'd pop right up.
就算她在这里
If she's even here.
你们为什么一开始就这么确定
How can you guys be so sure
她会从未来时空回来
that she even came back from the future in the first place?
因为是斯旺派她来的
Because Thawne sent her.
他教会了她时间旅行的新方式
He showed her a new way to time-travel,
是我们无法检测到的
something that can't be detected.
但只要她再开始奔跑
But as soon as she starts running again,
我们就能找到她  带她回家
we're gonna be able to bring her home.
闪电小队
Well, Team Flash,
诺拉·韦斯特·艾伦不是唯一消失的时间旅行者
Nora West-Allen is not the only time traveler who's absent.
我们一直在巡查废弃大楼  止赎公寓
We've been running down abandoned buildings, foreclosed condos...
任何格蕾丝·吉本斯
Anywhere that Grace Gibbons
可能隐藏小时候的她的地方  但是
may have hidden her younger self, but--
我们一无所获
We got bupkis.
而且我们也不知道她为什么要偷走制冷雾化器
And we have no idea why she stole the Cryo-Atomizer,
它除了能杀死我爸  也没有其他用处
except that it was worth killing my dad for.
如果你还需要点时间
Hey, if you need more time...
我们几个完全有能力
Yeah, we're more than capable of chasing
追捕她们两个
a wild goose or two on our own.
谢谢  我没事
Thank you, I'm fine.
我宁愿工作
I'd rather be working.
说到那个  我很乐意帮你
On that note, I'm happy to help you
寻找雾化器的下落
follow that lead on the atomizer.
真的吗
Really?
-那歇拉克呢  -歇洛克
- What about... Sherluck? - Sherloque.
你们这些人就没有一个能说对我的名字
Do you think any of you will get this right at any point
哪怕一次吗  是歇洛克
at any time in your life? Sherloque.
我看是没有  我还是继续
No, I'm going to continue
搜查诺拉·韦斯特·艾伦的下落吧
the quest for Nora West-Allen.
这事我多少得负点责
I... feel somewhat responsible.
中城警局有消息  有一起闯入事件发生在
Hey, it's CCPD-- there was a break-in
34大道和威廉姆森区交叉段的一家建筑公司
at an architecture firm on 34th and Williamson.
嫌犯是超能力者
Meta-suspect.
有公民报告那里发生过爆炸
Citizens reporting an explosion there.
听起来你们或许需要帮手的协助
Sounds like you guys might need an extra set of hands.
我去戴上我的震波设备
I'll grab my gear.
我爸爸北极旧实验室的警报响了
Oh. There's an alert at my dad's old lab in the Arctic.
我们得去看看
We should check it out.
没问题  我最好回去把秋裤洗洗带上
Yeah, better wash my long johns.
没错
Yeah.
你要接电话吗  还是
You gonna get that or...
当然  我会接的
Yeah, I'm going to get it,
但我已经知道是瑞内·奥德勒打来的了
but I know already it's Renée Aldler--
-艾德勒  -艾德勒
- Adler. - Adler.
还有她发给我的这些图释象形图
With these emoticon pictogram things that she send me.
像你这样的侦探大师都看不懂几个表情包吗
Oh, master detective like you can't decode a few emojis?
我能破译这些表情包  完全没问题好吗
I can decode these emojis no problem, huh?
爱心  她喜欢我  亲亲  想亲我呗
Heart, she like me. Kissy face, want to kiss me.
桃子  茄子  她喜欢水果和蔬菜
Peach, eggplant, she like fruit and vegetable.
在这点上  和其他的瑞内·奥德勒一样
At this point with the other Renée Aldlers,
我们向来坦诚相见
we are not keeping secrets from one another.
我看完了
Well, I did it.
每个训练  每个意图
Every exercise, every intention,
现在我和卡米拉过得挺好
and now that Kamilla and I are hunky-dory...
你看完了拉尔夫之书
You have completed the Book of Ralph.
-没错  -谢谢你的服务
- I sure did. - Thank you for your service,
老伙计  但你的工作还没完呢
old friend, but your job isn't done yet.
歇里  你想你会用得上它的
Shirley, I think you could use this.
不用  不用
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
怎么了  你觉得我需要帮忙分手吗
What, do you think I need help with a breakup?
拜托  听我说  附录C
Oh, come on. Look, Addendum C...
附录四
Appendix four.
让你们关系更进一层的指南
A guide to taking your relationship to the next level.
在西斯科身上很奏效
It worked for Cisco.
也就对小拉尔夫·马奇奥来说勉强有用
Barely worked for young Ralph Macchio.
不不不  这个人  他是小鸡  对吧
No, no, no. This guy, he's chicken, right?
即使是在现行恋爱关系中
Even in his current relationship,
他都害怕告诉女朋友
he's too afraid to tell this girl
他就是震波的事实  对吧
that he's actually Vibe, right?
我其实不是害怕
I'm actually not afraid.
我准备好了自然会告诉她的
I'm gonna tell her when I'm ready.
只是因为要想平衡超能力者
It's just hard to navigate
和普通人的生活模式很难罢了
the meta-life, personal-life balance.
说是平衡人鸡生活模式还差不多
More like chicken-life balance, hmm?
你才是平衡人鸡生活模式
Man, you're a chicken personal-life balance.
只要我想  随时都能告诉她
I can tell her whenever I want.
好啊  那你为什么不现在就告诉她
Well, then tell her right now, why don't you?
你想让我现在就告诉她
You want me to tell her right now?
-没错  -那我现在就告诉她
-Yeah. - I'll tell her right now.
我只是  你懂的
I just got--well, you know.
我手机在电梯里信号不稳定
I have spotty reception in the elevator.
那就出来打电话告诉她
Come on out and do it.
我得去工作了
Well, you know, I gotta get to work.
-出来打电话告诉她  -我得去工作了
- Come on out and do it. - I gotta get to work.
西蒙与伙伴公司
我刚和这里的一位建筑师谈过了
I just talked to one of the architects here,
西蒙与伙伴公司
and G. Simone & Associates
经常做一些备受瞩目的设计工作
used to do all of this high-profile design work--
赌场  银行和军事基地
casinos, banks, military bases--
但是显然在去年
but apparently, last year,
他们一直与一位匿名的客户合作
they had been working with an anonymous client.
所以因为我们要找的小偷掩盖了踪迹
So because our thief covered his tracks,
我们完全不知道那个客户是什么人
we have no idea who that client might be.
来看看这里
Look at this.
看看这些硬盘
Look at these hard drives.
彻底烧焦了  就像是遇到了大量的电涌
Fried from the inside, like in a massive power surge.
这种服务器应该有电涌保护器对吧
A server like this would have a surge protector, right?
特有的金属氧化变阻器
A typical metal-oxide varistor
能抵御一千焦耳
protects against a thousand joules.
闪电有多少焦耳
How many joules does a lightning bolt have?
十亿焦耳
A billion.
什么  你觉得是诺拉干的
What, you think this was Nora?
不  这不可能
No, this couldn't have been.
我们的扫描仪会侦测到她
I mean, our scanners would've picked her up.
说到这个
Yeah, about that--
我刚刚接收到一大堆背景粒子辐射
I just picked up a frak-ton of background particle radiation.
粒子  超光子吗
Particles? Tachyons?
负超光子
Negative tachyons.
有这种东西吗
That's a thing?
负超光子不能产生闪电吧
I mean, negative tachyons can't generate lightning, right?
除非负超光子
Unless negative tachyons
不像我们所想的那样抵消正超光子
don't just offset positive ones like we thought.
也许负超光子抽取正超光子
Maybe they actually siphon positive tachyons.
就像寄生虫一样从神速力里偷取速度吗
Stealing speed from the Speed Force like a parasite?
斯旺就是这么教她的
That's what Thawne taught her how to do.
她利用负超光子来奔跑  避开我们的扫描仪
She's using negative tachyons to run and avoid our scanners.
但是诺拉为什么要避开我们呢
Yeah, but why would Nora be trying to avoid us?
我不知道  但如果她要窃取蓝图
I don't know, but if she's stealing blueprints,
这里不会是她的最后一站
this ain't gonna be her last stop.
喷漆很漂亮
Pretty paint job.
掠夺者知道这些颜色会让人眼前一亮
Predators know these colors get you stung.
对于小偷吸引别人注意力
Yeah, it's always a great idea
这一直是不错的办法
for a thief to draw attention to herself.
至少我不用穿着一件毛茸茸的绿毛衣到处跑
At least I don't fly around in a fuzzy green sweater.
你认为我认不出天气巫师的孩子吗
Didn't think I'd recognize Weather Wizard's kid?
是天气女巫  我有名字的好吗
It's Weather Witch. I have a name, okay?
暴眼大盗
Bug-Eyed Bandit.
别这么叫我  那是他们起的
Don't call me that. That's their name.
我听说你在星城的机器人蜜蜂之举
I heard you took your robot bee act to Star City.
是和治疗脊椎肿瘤有关吗
Something about curing a spinal tumor?
我还听说你和你的另一半在玻利维亚
Well, I heard you and your other half were in Bolivia.
还是说银色幽灵放你鸽子了
Or did Silver Ghost ditch you?
拉娅·范赞特说有个大买卖
Van Zandt talked a big game.
她也想招募我
She tried to recruit me too.
她想我们叫什么
What did she want to call us?
小...
Young--
你是布娃娃对吧
Rag Doll, right?
你炸毁了西弗大楼
You blew up the Seaver Building.
真"蜜"丽
Bee-utiful.
我该感谢谁神秘地邀请我呢
And whom do I thank for my mysterious invitation?
等等  我也收到了匿名邀请
Wait, I got an anonymous offer too.
不是你吗
This wasn't your job?
我还以为是你
I thought this was your job.
其实是我邀请你们来的
Actually, I invited you.
你想我们替你做事吗
You want us to work for you?
不是替我  是和我一起
Not for me. With me.
一块大饼分四份
One big score split four ways.
有什么附带条件  伪善人
What's the catch, goody two shoes?
没有附带条件  不耍花招  只有一个要求
No catches, no tricks. Just one condition.
不能杀人
No killing.
虽然很好玩  各位  我退出
Well, this has been really fun, guys, I'm out.
如果有人死了  警察会满城追捕我们
If anybody dies, the cops will be all over us.
你就喜欢这样吧
Yeah, you would love that, huh?
我很惊讶闪电侠还没来
I was surprised that the Flash isn't already here.
我不再跟他合作了
I'm not working with him anymore.
你可以穿上皮衣
Look, you can put on your leather
想怎么叛逆就怎么叛逆
and you can act like a bad girl all you want,
但你永远也不是我们的一员
but you will never be one of us.
我们流冰区那次呢
What about the ice patch?
如果你不相信我
If you don't trust me,
你为什么不让那辆调查车从我身上碾过去
why did you stop that test car from running me over?
她说的是真的吗
Is she for real?
那里很冷
It was cold.
水结冰了
Water freezes.
不是那样的  并没有
Not like that, it doesn't.
过去这几个月  我经历了很多事
Look, these past few months, I have been through a lot.
我已经不是以前的我了
I'm not the same person I was.
证明给我们看
Okay. Prove it.
要干什么
What's the job?
麦克洛奇技术公司
McCulloch Technologies.
国内最大的
It's the largest manufacturer
军用武器制造商
of military-grade weapons in the country.
那极速者为什么要我们帮忙
So why does a speedster need our help
去砸窗打劫呢
to pull off a smash-and-grab?
麦克洛奇在这里制造和测试他们的武器
McCulloch builds and tests all of their weapons here.
铸造厂
The Forge.
这里受到超能力抑制器的保护
And it's protected by a meta-human dampener
让天眼会看起来像是灭虫器
that makes A.R.G.U.S.' look like a bug zapper.
你需要我们的技术  因为那不会受影响
So, you need us for our tech, because it won't be affected.
今晚麦克洛奇科技要举办一个展览
McCulloch's hosting an expo tonight.
可以掩护我们进入那栋楼
That'll give us cover to get on the property,
但进入铸造厂很棘手
but breaking into the Forge is where things get tricky.
这块饼不值得冒这么大的风险
There's no way this score is worth the risk.
看到这些武器了吗
Look. See these weapons?
里面还有上百件类似的
There's a hundred more like these inside.
每一件在黑市上都能卖上百万  轻而易举
Each will go for a million on the black market, easy.
我们只需先到一个地方停留一下
We just need to make one quick pit stop first.
我们要去打劫闪电侠
We need to rob the Flash.
我非常肯定蝉女来过这里
Okay, pretty safe bet She-Cada was here.
最好先四处检查一下
Better check it out.
看看能不能找出她拿走了什么
See if we can figure out what she took.
如果我能先让手指动起来
Yeah, that is if I can get my fingers to start moving again.
你觉得冰霜能不能来帮帮我们
You think there's any chance Frost could help us out
把上面的密封胶弄一弄
with some sealant up there?
我觉得她今天不会出来了
I don't think she's coming out today.
她还在为你爸的过世而难过吗
She still having a tough time with your dad's death?
冰霜保护了我这么久
I mean, Frost protected me for so long
我想她以前从来没有像这样
that I don't think she's ever felt pain of her own before,
感受过自己的痛苦
not like this.
这点我应该可以帮忙
Well, I-I think I could help with that.
给
Here.
《拉尔夫转移目标的哀悼27个步骤》
"Ralph's 27 Steps to a Better Mourning"?
我认为冰霜不会想看小册子
I don't think Frost would respond very well to a pamphlet.
拜托  看看吧
Oh, come on. Look.
第十条  去看牙医
Uh, number 10: go see your dentist
因为一年至少应该去看两次牙医
because you should be doing that at least twice a year
你一直都在偷懒
and you've been slacking,
这让你有事情去做  而不是沉湎在痛苦里
and it'll give you something to do other than dwell on the pain.
我来了  你现在可以闭嘴了吧
There. Now will you shut up?
和你说了我能让她出来
Told you I'd get her to come out.
猜猜怎么样
Guess what?
西蒙与伙伴公司前一年一直在为
G. Simone & Associates has spent the last year
麦克洛奇科技工作
working for McCulloch Technologies.
那个武器制造商吗
The weapons manufacturer?
他们刚在楔石城建了厂
They just built a factory in Keystone.
失踪的蓝图  高度机密的设施
Missing blueprints. Top-secret facility.
我想我们面对的是一场抢劫
I think we might have a heist on our hands.
你觉得诺拉是冲着那些武器去的吗
You think Nora's going after these weapons?
不  或许她是想把那些武器清理出市场
No, maybe she's just trying to get them off the market.
你知道  就像是那次巴里和拉尔夫
You know, like the time that Barry and Ralph
去买"宴会主持人"时一样
were gonna buy the Toastmasters.
她是在为斯旺做事
She's on a mission for Thawne.
他不会目光这么短
He doesn't think that small.
巴里正在扫描负超光子
Hey, Barry is scanning for negative tachyons.
你和我为什么不去挖掘下
Why don't you and I dig
麦克洛奇在制造什么样的武器
into what kind of weapons McCulloch is making?
我在国土安全局认识一个线人
I know this whistleblower down at the DOD.
也许她能有点什么线索
Maybe she could offer some insight.
爱瑞丝  你确定没有别的事
Iris, are you sure there isn't anything else
想要说吗
you'd like to talk about?
当我在2049年见到诺拉时
Look.... when I saw Nora in 2049,
她非常沮丧  非常愤怒
she was so upset and so angry,
但是她知道我想带她回来
but she knew that I wanted to bring her back.
然后她回到这个时间
Then she comes back to this time
但是却连家都不回
and--and she doesn't even come home?
我是说  即便她在生巴里的气
I mean, even if she's mad at Barry
或是想要什么科幻武器
or she wanted some kind of sci-fi weapon--
她为什么不直接找我们来帮忙
Then why didn't she just come to the rest of us for help?
肯定是有原因的
There's gotta be a good reason.
我知道
I know it.
别这样  诺拉
Come on, Nora.
她在躲避我们  她还偷了蓝图
She's avoiding us. She's stealing blueprints.
我是说  她可会惹上大麻烦的
I mean, she could really get into trouble out there.
但你认为找到她就能带回她吗
But you think she'll return if you do find her?
毕竟  她有很好的理由生我们的气
After all, she has good reason to be angry at all of us.
什么  别把我卷进你俩的事里
Uh, what? Don't lump me in with you two.
我很生气  她也很生气
I was pissed. She was pissed.
但我们都有时间  冰释前嫌
But we've both had time to... get over it,
她还是诺拉
and she's still Nora.
如果我告诉她可以回家了
If I tell her she can come home again,
我肯定她会放弃为斯旺工作
I'm sure she'll stop working with Thawne.
发现信号
地点 实验室档案馆
那是诺拉吗
Is that Nora?
肯定是的
It has to be.
她在实验室档案馆
She's in the Starchives.
诺拉
Nora.
爸爸
Hi, Dad.
你要去哪里
Hey, where you going?
诺拉也是我的责任
Nora is my responsibility as well.
我必须和她谈谈
I must speak with her.
别关门
Hey, hold that!
我们下水道系统里的动态感应被触发了
One of our motion sensors just got tripped in the sewage system.
下水道系统
Sewage system?
不可能  没人能挤进那里
Mais non. Nobody could fit down there.
那是斯宾塞·扬的手机吗
Is that Spencer Young's phone?
你要做什么
What are you doing?
我说了你也不会相信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
诺拉
Nora...
我不应该就那样处理事情
I shouldn't have left things the way that I did.
好吗
All right?
我想让你回家
I want you to come home.
我们都想
We all do.
你只需要放弃和斯旺合作
You just have to stop working with Thawne.
目标获取
Target acquired.
收到
Copy that.
你在和谁讲话吗
Are you talking to someone?
你觉得我在和斯旺说话吗
What do you think, I'm talking to Thawne?
他在未来  爸爸  可不是随便就能通话
He's in the future, Dad. I can't exactly call him up.
我没那么说
I didn't say that.
是  但是你说只要我还和他合作
Yeah, but you did say that I couldn't come home
就不能回家
if I was still working with him.
-你还是不信任我  -诺拉  信任需要时间
- You still don't trust me. - Nora, trust takes time.
那什么能阻止你下一次
Then what's to stop you from sending me back
生我气的时候再送我回去
the next time you get pissed at me?
什么都不能
Nothing.
因为你再一次抛弃了我
Because you've given up on me again.
就像你每次都会抛弃我一样
Given up on me like you do every time!
诺拉  你在做什么
Nora, what are you doing?
我回来这里是见你的
You know, I came back here to meet you.
但我一到这里  你就疏远我
And the second I got here, you started pushing me away.
然后你把我扔在未来
And then you left me in the future.
你就那么把我扔在大街上
You just dumped me in the middle of the street
转身就走
and walked away!
你得停下
You have to stop.
你也没和妈妈一起来接我回去
And you didn't come with Mom to bring me back.
因为你不想让我在这里  你根本不想要我
Because you don't want me here. You don't want me at all!
-诺拉  求你了  -我恨你
- Nora, please! - I hate you!
诺拉闯入了实验室档案馆
Nora broke into the Starchives.
抱歉  发生了什么
I'm sorry, what happened?
诺拉  闯入了实验室档案馆
Nora broke into the Starchives.
我以为我能阻止她  但我办不到
I thought I could stop her, but I couldn't.
她偷走了斯宾塞·扬的手机
She stole Spencer Young's phone.
斯宾塞·扬那个催眠手机吗
Spencer Young's hypnotizing phone?
-是的  -巴里  没事的
- Yes. - Barry, it's okay.
你搞清楚她想做什么了吗
Did you at least find out what she's doing?
没有  我试过了
No, no. I tried.
我以为我能劝她回家
I-I thought I could convince her to come home.
但是
But...
她的脸开始震动  然后...
her face started vibrating, and...
然后她的眼睛
and then her eyes...
她的闪电
her lightning...
变成红色了
it was red.
就和他的一样
Just like his.
我以为我们还有时间找回她
I thought we had time to reach her,
但是他抢先了一步
but he got to her.
斯旺完全控制了她
Thawne really got to her.
各位
Uh, guys,
警告
电脑上有个红色标志在闪
there's a blinky red light thing on the computer.
尖端科研实验室的又一个警报响了
Another alarm went off at S.T.A.R. Labs.
各位  这个是五分钟之前的
Guys, this was only five minutes ago.
乔斯·贾科姆和彼得·梅克尔
Joss Jackam and Peter Merkel?
他们是怎么进到尖端科研实验室的
How would they get into S.T.A.R. Labs?
诺拉之前在和人通话
Nora had someone in her ear.
这是一次协作袭击
It was a coordinated assault.
但这意味着她正在和
But that would mean that she's working...
他们合作
with them.
钡
Barium.
咱们在楔石城
We're in Keystone City.
我们这有布娃娃
Well, we got a Rag Doll,
天气女巫  还有
a Weather Witch, and, uh...
等下  你是那个疯子蜜蜂女吗
hold up, is that crazy bee girl?
姑娘  最近怎么样
Hey, girl! What's going on?
真是太怀旧了
What a throwback.
他在这里做什么
What the hell is he doing here?
你在这里做什么
What the hell are you doing here?
不
Oh, no.
她和他们是一伙的
She's with them.
我说我只要拉蒙  不需要其他人
I said I wanted Ramon. No one else.
好吧  他们当时在一起
Yeah, well, they were together,
你说不能杀人  所以他们才在这里
and you said no killing, so here they are.
杀人
Killing?
这部手机同步了斯宾塞·扬的DNA
This phone was synced to Spencer Young's DNA.
我们要你破解译码  让我们能够使用它
We need you to hack past the coding so we're able to use it.
你在笑什么
Why are you laughing?
对不起  我不是故意揭穿你  狂热粉丝
I'm sorry, I don't mean to blow up your spot, fangirl,
你看  这只是...
you see, it's just, um...
我以前也做过同样的事情
I've done this exact same thing before.
我们要黑进武器  我们来绑架西斯科吧
We need to hack a weapon. Let's kidnap Cisco.
你加入了侠盗翻唱乐队还是什么
I mean, what, did you join a Rogues cover band or something?
这个翻唱乐队怎么样
How's this for a cover band?
老招  不过挺管用
Oldie but a goodie.
听着  XS  我欠你一个道歉
Look, XS, I owe you an apology, hmm?
我不应该以这种方式来揭发你的秘密
Never should've exposed your secret the way I did.
我将尊严置于家人之上  欺骗自己
I put my pride in front of the family that took me in--
你的家人  你的家人很爱你
your family-- and your family loves you.
我敢肯定你已经听过
I'm sure you heard.
今天你父亲告诉你够多的了  对吧
Your father told you as much today, right?
你去见了你的父亲
You saw your father?
你说你去抢劫闪电侠
You said you were robbing the Flash.
不  不  你还不明白吗
No. No, don't you get it?
他的父亲就是闪电侠
Her old man is the Flash.
听着  你们不必操心闪电侠的事  好吗
Look, you don't have to worry about the Flash, okay?
只需要让拉蒙开始破解手机
Just get Ramon started on that phone.
靴子磨损痕迹
Boot scuff marks.
我认为她撞到这台东西
I'm thinking she hit this thing.
是的
Yeah.
电解质注射液
Intravenous electrolytes.
这些可以用于治疗昏迷患者
I mean, those can be used to treat coma patients.
所以她抢这些应该是给童年格蕾丝的
So maybe she grabbed them for Grace Junior.
肯定是
Hell, yeah.
我就知道你那套《实习医生格蕾》能派得上用场
I knew your "Grey's Anatomy" Thing would come in handy.
拉尔夫  你到底为什么要带我来这里
Ralph, why did you really bring me here?
是为了帮助我和冰霜杀手吗
Was it to help Killer Frost and me?
就像你帮助西斯科忘记吉普赛
The same way you helped Cisco get over Gypsy
歇洛克忘记瑞内那样吗
and Sherloque with Renée?
你在说什么  我们是一个团队
What are you talking about? I mean, we're a team.
这是我们该做的  互相照应
It's what we do. We help each other.
是的  但你从西斯科手中拿回拉尔夫之书后
Yeah, but the minute you got the Book of Ralph back from Cisco,
你又想把它送给别人
you tried to give it away again.
你难道不想用它吗
Don't you want to use it?
尝试给自己找一位特别的人
Try and find someone special for yourself?
凯特琳
Caitlin...
听着
look...
拉尔夫之书
Book of Ralph...
很适合其他人用  但是
works great for other people, but...
但从来都不适合我
never actually worked for me.
我知道我不是
I know I'm not...
为爱而生
built for love.
这没关系
And that's okay.
拉尔夫·德比  你善良聪慧  富有同情心
Ralph Dibny, you are kind, intelligent, and compassionate.
但最重要的是
And most of all,
你将他人的需求置于自己的需求之上
you put the needs of others before yourself.
所以这意味着  你是为爱而生的
So that means you are built for love,
你值得有人回应你的爱
and you deserve someone who loves you back.
凯特琳
Caitlin...
我很抱歉  但我对你没有感觉
I'm sorry, I just don't feel that way about you.
好恶心
Ugh. Gross!
拜托  你这笨蛋
Oh, come on, you idiot.
对不起  我  我搞错了
Sorry, I got my-- I got my wires crossed.
老天
Jeez.
话说
Hey...
我觉得这个冰箱
I think this might be the fridge
就是西斯科告诉我的那个
that Cisco was telling me about,
他改装的恒温箱
the one that he rewired as an incubator.
现在顶层架子是空的
And now the top shelf is empty.
好吧  顶层架子之前放了什么
Okay, what was on the top shelf?
西斯科的超能力解药原型
Cisco's prototypes for the meta-human cure.
我想我知道蝉在密谋些什么了
I think I know what Cicada is planning.
上次一群女人把我绑成这样
Last time a group of women had me tied up like this--
是你的前妻们
They were your ex-wives?
不  是他们的律师  实际上
No, their attorneys, actually.
我是不是会跟你一个下场
Am I gonna end up like you?
和工作结婚
Married to the job?
向我认识的所有人隐藏秘密
Keeping secrets from everyone I know?
实际上  在我目前这段感情中
Well, actually, in my current romance,
我不是那个隐藏秘密的人
I'm not the one keeping secrets.
不  不  我遇见了瑞内·奥德勒
No, no, I meet Renée Aldler--
-艾德勒  -然后我发现
- Adler-- - And then I discover...
她是超能力者
she's a meta-human.
她没有告诉过你吗
And she hasn't told you yet?
没有  先生  你敢相信吗
No, monsieur. Can you believe that?
所以假如你知道真相  但你深藏心中
So if you know the truth, and you're bottling it in,
不也意味着你有点不诚实吗
doesn't that mean you're kind of being dishonest?
鸡能认出同类
Chicken recognize chicken.
然而  你真的是一只鸡吗
And yet, are you really a chicken...
咯咯先生
Monsieur Bawk?
还是你不和卡麦拉分享秘密身份
Or are you not sharing your secret identity with Kamala--
-卡米拉  -因为...
- Kamilla. - Because...
你没有超级满意自己的秘密身份
you're not super-satisfied with your secret identity?
你是说我不想成为震波吗
Are you saying I don't want to be Vibe?
我们一起来审视证据  好吗
Well, let's examine the evidence, shall we?
去年的上半年你没有超能力
You spent this past year sans powers for the first part,
下半年在治愈超能力
and the second part curing powers.
也许对卡麦拉坦诚...
Perhaps being honest with Kamala...
卡米拉
Kamilla.
需要你先对自己坦诚
Begins with being honest with yourself.
好好想一下
Think about that.
我们知道的是诺拉组队
So what we know is that Nora put together a team
是为了闯入这里  麦克洛奇技术公司
to break into here, McCulloch Technologies,
武器制造商
a weapons manufacturer.
但不只是武器
But not just any weapons.
这帮家伙还和城市签约
The city has contracted these guys
负责清理尖端实验室的卫星碎片
to clean up the shrapnel from the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite.
让我猜猜  碎片废物都没有被处理到垃圾场
Let me guess: none of that crap ended up in the dump.
他们用来制造超能科技
They used it to make meta-tech
就像斯宾塞·扬的手机
like Spencer Young's phone.
我的线人说今晚麦克洛奇
My source says that McCulloch is debuting
有新产品系列上市
a new line of products tonight.
这真是闯入的完美掩护
That's a perfect cover-up for a break-in.
我们对于诺拉的动机有推测吗
We have any theory on Nora's motive?
实际上  蝉的匕首会抑制
Actually, Cicada's dagger dampens the abilities
附近超能力者的能力
of meta-humans nearby,
但是对超能科技没有影响
but it wouldn't have any effect on meta-tech.
所以诺拉可能想抓住蝉
So maybe Nora wants to catch Cicada?
或者做更严重的事
Or do something worse.
巴里  这不可能
Barry, there's no way.
这就是我所担心的事  爱瑞丝
This is exactly what I was afraid of, Iris.
斯旺一直在操纵她
Thawne's been manipulating her.
现在她的举止言谈都像他
Now she's acting like him, talking like him.
这不代表她有能力杀蝉
That doesn't mean that she's capable of killing Cicada.
她和无赖帮合作
She's working with Rogues.
她绑架了西斯科和歇洛克
She kidnapped Cisco and Sherloque.
我们不知道她还能做出什么
We don't know what she's capable of.
所以你想做什么  巴仔
So what do you want to do, Barr?
我们把她关起来
We bring her in.
我们用西斯科的力场  雷的纳米机器人
We use Cisco's force fields,Ray's nanites--
我们把她关起来
we're bringing her in,
在她踏入那栋楼之前
before she steps anywhere near that building.
巴里  等等
Hey, Barry. Hold on.
我们不能一直把诺拉
We can't keep treating Nora
当成超级坏人一样对待
like she's some kind of super-villain, okay?
这样只会将她推远
We're just gonna push her away.
我们能做什么呢
What are we supposed to do?
任由她利用我们吗
Just let her keep taking advantage of us?
不  我们去了解她
No. We see where she's coming from.
我们试着弄明白她为什么这么做
We try to figure out why she's doing this.
和为什么没有关系  爱瑞丝
It doesn't matter why, Iris!
这是斯旺
This is Thawne.
是他的计划
It's his plan.
也许他的计划不那么坏
Well, maybe his plan isn't so bad.
什么
What?
也许
Maybe--
我认为
I thought--
我以为我们谈过了
I thought we were past this, it's--
她不可以和斯旺合作
it's not okay for her to work with Thawne.
你见过他了  你说他在操控她
You saw him. You said he's manipulating her.
我还说了他在乎她
And I said that he cares about her.
他关心她的安危
He's worried about her safety--
不  他需要她  爱瑞丝  他需要她
No, he needs her, Iris. He needs her.
或者  他变了
Or... he's changed.
巴里  是斯旺说服我
Barry, Thawne is the one that convinced me
回家试着解决和你的矛盾
to come back home and try and patch things up with you.
斯旺
Thawne.
斯旺给你建议
Thawne gave you advice?
听着  我知道听起来很疯狂
Look, I know it sounds insane,
我知道对你来说一定很困难
and I know this must be hard for you to hear,
但是  巴里  自从我回家
but, Barry, ever since I got back home,
我的脑海里一直回荡着一个问题
the same question keeps running through my mind.
如果诺拉是对的呢
What if Nora is right?
万一斯旺真的想救赎自己
What if Thawne really is trying to redeem himself
他确实想阻止蝉
and that he does want to stop Cicada
诺拉没有回家的唯一原因
and the only reason that Nora hasn't come back home
是她知道你不相信她
is because she knows that you don't trust her?
听着
Look...
巴里  我们的生命里有诺拉
Barry, having Nora in our lives
让我们成为更好的人
has made us better people.
有没有可能
Isn't it possible
她同样影响了斯旺
that she did the same thing to Thawne?
访客  限制权限
珍妮·奥甘特中尉
珍妮·奥甘特
Jenni Ognats?
我以为重点是不引人注意
I thought the idea was to not draw attention.
现在你知道我爸是闪电侠
Oh, what, so now that you know my dad's the Flash,
你不相信我了
you don't trust me?
是你不相信我们
Hey, you're the one who doesn't trust us.
对不对
Isn't that right...
诺拉
Nora?
你的秘密身份  没什么隐瞒价值
Yeah, your secret identity, it's really not worth much.
感觉最近我这个人都没什么价值
Feels like nothing about me is worth much lately.
我爸离开了我
My dad left me,
即使我做了所有事帮他
after everything that I've done to try and help him.
你知道最尴尬的是什么吗
You know what the most embarrassing part is?
我心中还有一小部分
There's this tiny, little, weak part of me
依然希望他可以走进门
that still wants him to walk through that door
带我回家
and take me home.
我爸把我妈留在产科病房离开了
My dad left my mom at the maternity ward.
她没法看着我而不想到他
She couldn't look at me without seeing him.
她确保我知道这点
She made sure I knew it too.
所以我13岁那天离家出走了
So the day I turned 13, I ran.
起初我还在镇上
I didn't leave town at first.
我和其他出走的人一起呆在立交桥下
I stayed under the overpass with all the other runaways.
我坚信
And I thought for sure,
某天晚上  我会抬头
one night, I'd look up
见到我妈妈
and I'd see my mom.
她从未出现
She never showed.
-我很抱歉  -我不这么想
- Sorry. - I'm not.
当人们告诉你
When people tell you that
家人一直会在你身边
family is always gonna be there for you,
全是狗屁
they're full of it.
导师总会让你失望
Mentors will always let you down eventually.
父母会毁了你
Parents will break you.
对
Yeah.
所以我们要坚守在一起
That's why we have to stick together.
-是  -做好了
- Yeah. - Hey, it's done.
来吧  宅男破解了手机
Come on. Nerd's done with the phone.
一部重新编程的超能力技术手机
One reprogrammed meta-tech phone,
现在有了视觉和听觉催眠的能力
now with visual and auditory hypnosis capabilities.
加上无限制的数据
Plus unlimited data.
你现在会放了我们吗
You gonna let us go now?
然后你可以回去找闪电侠
What, so you can run right back to the Flash?
你以为我傻吗
How stupid do you think I am?
里面有病毒吗
Any bugs in there?
-没有  -很好
- It's clean. - Good.
现在确保他们不能做其他事
Now make sure they can't try anything else.
包围目标
来吧
Come on.
这票不会自动干成的
This score's not gonna steal itself.
这次你逃不掉的
You're not gonna get away with this.
我逃不掉吗
I'm not gonna get away with it?
西斯科的旧极速者陷阱
Cisco's old speedster trap.
你觉得对诺拉管用吗
You think that's gonna work for Nora?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不确定我想知道
I'm not sure I'm ready to find out, though.
听着  我很抱歉
Hey, look, I'm sorry about, um...
我之前的反应
how I was acting earlier, I just...
看到诺拉那么像他
seeing Nora looking so much like him...
我明白  巴仔
No, I get it, Barr.
那个人会一直影响你
That guy's always gonna be in your head.
对我也是
Mine too.
你是对的
And you were right.
诺拉违法了
Nora broke the law.
是应该有所应对
And there should be repercussions for that.
但是每当你们越界时
But whenever you guys step out of bounds,
我始终要提醒自己
I always have to remind myself,
作为警探的我说遵守法律
the detective side says there's the law.
作为父亲的我说要考虑对错
But the father side says there's also what's right.
我始终会首先选择做父亲
And... I'm always gonna choose to be your father first.
也许这就是我的问题
Maybe that's my problem.
什么
What?
我准备好了放弃她
I was ready to give up on her.
你知道  如果我准备好了这么做
You know, I mean, If I'm ready to do that,
会让我觉得
it makes me feel like...
即使我们一起经历了那么多
even after everything we've been through,
我不是一个好家长
I'm not a good parent.
也许从来不会是
You know, I mean, maybe I never will be.
巴仔  你知道不是这样的
Come on, Barry. You know that's not true.
你会成为一个很棒的父亲
You're going to be an amazing father.
我之前想让她离开
I wanted her to leave.
她一到这  我就
The second that she got here, I did, I...
我对她很抗拒
I've held back from her.
听到她叫我爸爸还是很别扭
It still doesn't feel right when she calls me Dad.
你也一直没叫我爸爸  直到
Well, you didn't call me Dad till--
直到在这  在这个房间
it was here, in this room,
你获得了你的超能力之后
right after you got your powers.
但你知道为什么
But you know why that was.
你有自己的父亲  亨利
You already had a dad. Henry.
当整个世界都认为
And when the whole world thought that
他是罪犯  巴里  你
that man was a criminal, Barr, you...
你认为他是完美的
You thought he was perfect.
你觉得爱瑞丝是对的吗
Do you think Iris is right?
诺拉的计划  斯旺的计划
Nora's plan, Thawne's plan...
能是一件好事吗
could be a good thing?
我不相信那个家伙
I don't trust that man.
我之前不相信  今后也不会
I never have and I never will.
但我的确
But I do...
相信我的外孙女
trust my granddaughter.
如果我们要把诺拉带回家  巴里
And if we're gonna bring Nora home, Barr...
你也得相信她
you're gonna have to trust her too.
谢谢克罗姆
Oh, thank Crom.
我或许给了你无限数据
I might've given you unlimited data,
但我也给了你糟糕的信号接收
but I also gave you spotty reception.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
好了  蜜蜂已处于无人模式了
All right. The bees are in drone mode.
所以如果我们移动得很慢很慢
So if we move very, very slowly--
老兄  究竟怎么回事
Man, what in the world?
什么
What?
我在五十一号地球上
I was trained in the art of escape
师从撒迪厄斯·布朗学习逃跑术
by Thaddeus Brown from Earth-51.
是吗  那帮我逃跑啊
Yeah, well, help me escape!
好计划
That's a good plan.
所以
So, um...
-从十开始倒数  -十
- Count backwards from ten. - Ten--
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
-商业机密  -好吧
- Trade secret. - Okay.
所以
So...
你不具防火性能对不  拉蒙先生
You're not fireproof, are you, Monsieur Ramon?
我防  天啊
Am I fire-- oh, God.
不不
No, no.
是全部的吗
That's all of them?
-我想是  -太好了
- I think so. - Good.
因为诺拉·韦斯特-艾伦现在十分危险
Because Nora West-Allen is in grave danger.
感谢您的耐心  女士们先生们
Thank you for your patience, ladies and gentlemen.
我们今晚展示的这种技术
With the kind of technology we're displaying tonight,
安全高于一切
security is our highest priority.
请出示参观者证件
Visitor IDs, please.
当然
You bet.
扫描中
有效证件
好了  我们走  这边请女士们
Okay, here we go. Right this way, ladies.
过去在麦克洛奇的十个月
The last ten months have been
非常令人激动
very exciting here at McCulloch.
陆军海军的买家已经
Buyers from the Army and Navy are already waiting for us
在我们的尖端样本室等着我们了
in our state-of-the-art demo room.
那扇门后面是什么
Uh, what's behind that door?
这是我们的工程师称为锻造间的地方
That's what our engineers have dubbed the Forge.
是我们研发和测试新武器的地方
It's where we develop and test our new weapons.
不幸的是  能进去那里的
Unfortunately, it's only accessible to employees
只有拥有最高安全等级的员工
with the highest security clearance.
记住
Remember.
不许杀人
No killing.
这是蒙哥马利四千  三十吨的保险库门
That's a Montgomery 4000, 30-ton vault door.
只能从里面打开
It'll only open from the inside,
所以进入锻造间的唯一路径就是那
so the only way into the Forge is through there.
好舒服
Mm, cozy.
准备好了吗  小丑
Ready, clown?
你确定你能从那东西进去
Are you sure you can fit through that thing?
正对我的胃口
This shall be my aria.
记住  你一旦进去那边
Remember, once you get to the other side,
阻尼器会立即使你的超能力消失
the dampener will take away your powers,
所以赶快出来
so get out quick.
我要吐了
Yeah, I'm gonna vomit.
芝麻开门
Open, sesame.
和人质待在一起
Stay with the hostages.
我们出来的时候会带上你
We'll grab you on the way out.
待会见
See you soon.
麦克洛奇
这超能力抑制器可真厉害
That's one serious meta-dampener.
计划最后一步
Last part of the plan.
装货
Load up.
对不起XS
Sorry, XS.
计划有变
Change of plans.
晚上好  中城
Good evening, Central City.
我们为大家准备了一场特别的演出
We've prepared a special show for you.
今晚的庆典
Tonight's festivities
由几个即将牺牲的工蜂主演
will feature several expendable worker bees--
麦克洛奇技术公司的员工
the employees of McCulloch Technologies.
除非闪电侠在三十秒内到达
Unless the Flash comes down here in the next 30 seconds
向世界揭示他的身份
and reveals his identity to the world.
古奇
Gucci?
你们不想要钱吗
You don't want the money?
不  我们想要
Oh, no. We want the money.
我们只是想先出个名
We just wanted to make a name for ourselves first.
所以暴露我爸能让你们正式成为无赖帮吗
So, what, outing my dad makes you legitimate Rogues?
我信任过你们
I trusted you.
天啊
Oh, God.
你听起来就像银色幽灵
You sound just like Silver Ghost...
我把她留在玻利维亚的时候
when I left her in Bolivia.
至少你会死得快点
At least you'll die fast.
我猜也差不多三十秒了吧
I'd say it's been about 30 seconds, right?
-是的  -是吗
- Yeah. - Right?
好的
Okay.
等下
Wait!
我到了
I am here.
好的  闪电侠
All right, Speedy.
给我看看你的真实身份  去掉面罩
Show us your true identity. Mask off.
爸  你不必如此的
Dad, please. You do not have to do this.
我必须
I have to.
我是一个
I am a man
独自坐在餐桌边的人
sitting alone at the dinner table.
他喝晕了吗
Is he drunk?
看到吗  当你位于
See, when you're in position
供养世界的位置上
to feed the world,
作为父亲会很困难
it can make it hard to be a father.
你得不断地问自己
You have to constantly ask yourself,
对世界来说什么是对的
is what's right for the world
对你的孩子来说什么是对的
what's right for your child?
我们能动手了吗
Hey, can we get on with it?
可以
Yes, um... yeah, uh...
-不  -什么
- No. - What?
你真的认为
Did you seriously think
我会再次上当吗
I was gonna fall for this again?
我穿过了你的攻击
I phase right through your blast.
你没法阻止闪电侠
Ha! You can't stop the Flash!
不  我想你被拆穿了
No, I think the jig is up.
糊涂了吗
Confused?
没必要
Don't be.
我的天
Holy shrap.
这怎么可能
How the hell is this even possible?
你们忙着处理通用云时我们绕开了警卫
We bypassed security while you were busy with General Cloud.
然后你们把我们这些工蜂直接带了进来
And then you walked us worker bees right inside.
你们人手不够  女士们  放下武器
You're outnumbered, ladies. Drop your weapons.
别让他击中抑制器
Don't let them hit that dampener.
把人质救出去
Get the hostages out of here.
我们来对付无赖帮
We'll handle the Rogues.
这边走
Okay, this way.
-我们得回去  -好
- We gotta get back in there. - Yeah.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
西斯科  我们需要恢复超能力
Cisco, we need our powers back.
你有办法对付这些蜜蜂吗
Can you do something about these bees?
再坚持一下
Hold tight.
爱瑞丝
Iris!
好吧  我们在这里坚持不了太久
All right, we're not gonna last here much longer.
我去分散她们的注意力
I'm gonna create a diversion.
准备好射击抑制器
Get ready to shoot the dampener.
不  爸爸  太危险了
No, no. Dad, it's too dangerous!
爸爸
Dad!
没把他从屋顶扔下去算他幸运
He's lucky I don't throw his ass off a roof.
没人能在科技上赢过我
Nobody out-techs me.
系统关闭
该死  拉蒙侵入了我的电话
Damn it. Ramon's in my phone.
这一下她肯定躲不过去
She's not getting out of this one alive.
诺拉  等等
Nora, wait!
爸爸  你被击中了
Dad! You've been hit.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
我不是唯一被击中的
I'm not the only one.
你就在我身边
You were here with me.
一直都是
The whole time.
我抛弃过你一次
I abandoned you once.
我永远不会再那样做
I'm never gonna do it again.
我们也许应该
So we should probably...
是的  绝对是
Oh, yeah. Definitely.
彼得·梅克尔
彼乔斯·贾科姆
布里·拉万
年轻无赖帮
The young Rogues.
他们可不算是你在那里交到的好朋友  宝贝
Not the nicest friends you made there, kiddo.
我以为我可以控制他们
Yeah, I... thought I could control them,
我们抓住他们之后再把武器偷回来
steal the weapons back after we lifted them,
但是我陷入了自己无法处理的事情
but I got in over my head.
即使是有充分的理由
Even if it was for a good reason.
诺拉  杀死蝉不是充分的理由
Nora, killing Cicada is not a good reason.
不  我不是想杀死蝉
No, I-I wasn't trying to kill Cicada.
我需要这个
I needed this.
这是由尖端科研实验室的卫星
It's a weapon built from the solar reflector panels
太阳能反光板做成的武器
from the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite,
可以把任何物体摧毁至原子状态
capable of destroying any object down to its atoms,
这是唯一能够摧毁蝉的匕首的东西
and it's the only thing that can destroy Cicada's dagger.
诺拉  你为什么不直接告诉我们
Nora, why didn't you just tell us this?
因为我不会相信她
Because I wouldn't have believed her.
因为这是斯旺的计划
'Cause it's Thawne's plan.
我知道爸爸有多生气
I knew how angry Dad was.
然后他没有和你一起去未来
And then you came to the future without him.
我以为他永远不会相信我了
I just thought he'd never believe me.
而且我还要在一点也不酷炫的心态里
Plus, I had to stay in a seriously unschway headspace
才能使用负神速力
to use the negative Speed Force.
但是现在我知道了
But I know now.
我再也不想离开你们
I don't ever want to leave you guys again.
如果这意味着不能继续斯旺的计划
And if that means not following through with Thawne's plan,
我觉得没关系
I'm okay with that.
我认为我们应该用它
I think we should use it.
你说什么
You what?
巴里  你确定吗
Barr, are you sure?
我们得阻止蝉
We have to stop Cicada.
我永远不会喜欢这个计划的出处
I'm never gonna like where this plan comes from.
但是如果它能起作用
But if this thing works...
听起来像是我们最好的机会
sounds like our best shot.
你真的相信他吗
You really believe him?
我相信你  诺拉
I believe in you, Nora.
我很抱歉没让你感受到这一点
And I'm sorry that I made you feel otherwise.
爸爸
Dad...
我之前说过的那些话
that stuff I said earlier--
是我活该
I deserved it.
我
I-I...
我不应该把你留在未来
I shouldn't have left you in the future.
我不应该给你回家加上条件
I shouldn't have put conditions on you coming home.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我爱你
I love you.
我们都爱你
We both do.
我们不会再离开你了  诺拉
We're never gonna leave you again, Nora.
我保证
I promise.
结论是什么
So what's the verdict?
诺拉说得对
Nora's story checks out.
这东西有一个棱镜电池
This thing has got a prismatic battery
给它的反光板充能
supercharging its reflector panels.
如果有什么能够摧毁那把匕首的话
So if anything's gonna destroy that dagger,
就是这支镜像枪
it's this mirror gun.
这或许是说得容易做起来难
That may be easier said than done.
为什么
Why's that?
我们发现了蝉从我爸爸的实验室拿走了什么
We figured out what Cicada took from my dad's lab.
是你的原型解药
It's your cure prototypes.
她为什么需要那个  它们只是原型
Why would she need those? They're just prototypes.
不  它们不止是原型
No, they're not just prototypes.
它们是失败和损坏版的解药
They're failed, broken versions of the cure.
如果超能力者接受它并且没有得到妥善处理
If a meta-human takes that without the proper treatment--
他们会死
They would die.
蝉手中拿着致命病毒
Cicada has a lethal virus on her hands.
这就是她偷走雾化器的原因
That's why she stole the atomizer.
这样她就可以散播病毒
So she can spread the virus.
她把解药变成了武器
She has weaponized the cure.
就是这样
This is it.
这就是噩梦
This is the nightmare.
蝉要杀死城里的所有超能力者
Cicada's gonna kill every meta-human in the city.
闪 电 侠
一只稀有的老鸟是鹈鹕
A rare, old bird is the pelican,
嘴能装的东西比肚子还多
whose beak can hold more than his belly can.
他的嘴可以装下
He can hold in his beak
一个星期的食物
enough food for a week.
但如果我知道
But I'm darned
他怎么做到的话
if I know
就怪了
how the hell he can.